行
Let's go.
快c 快c
Come on, come on.
嘿
Hey.
你能e吃@N|西了
Can you stop eating those?
怎么了
What?
嗯，有口臭
Well--they just kind of make your breath--
布R恩 我正在看
Brian, I'm watching this.
噢 只是新而已
Come on, it's just the news.
是啊 我正在看
Yeah, well, I'm watching.
真吲d
Well, that's discouraging.
怎么了
What?
看到你穿@身睡衣的r候我就知道
I guess I should have known when I saw those pajamas.
@是你的睡衣
They're your pajamas.
]e
Exactly.
@睡衣有什么}
What's wrong with them?
我是f 我以后都不上床了
l mean, are we ever gonna have sex again?
嘿，你想要怎
Hey, what do you want?
我不常面
We never see each other,
到面的r候 rg也不早了
and when we do, it's late,
我不怎么心 又很少出去s
and we haven't talked,and we don't go out,
所以在你（招妓）之前
so why don't you
就不能至少假b你喜g我
at least try acting like you like me before you--
我勰 你知道的
I love you.You know that.
我知道 布R恩
I know, Brian.
你知道 我真的很累了
You know what? I'm just really tired.
我跟安德・所_TM行F鲞B
We're going to take you live now to Andrew Solomon,
他在金斯堡槲做警方突谭ǖ默F蟮
who's in Wilkinsburg, where a police raid is in progress.
安德
Andrew?
你好 朱莉
Thank you, Julie.
]e 我F在正站在
That's right, I'm standing here at the corner
多佛和e夕法尼大道的街角
of Dover and Penn avenue,where a bust has
警方σ患
just occurred at an oriental massage parlor
涉嫌M行u淫活拥陌茨υ
where allegedly, a lot more than just massages
M行突谭
could be purchased.
F在^朋友可以看到
Now as you can see here,the police are in the
警方逮捕了酌犯罪嫌疑人
process of making several arrests.
F龅囊幻警官
One of the officers here...
私聊室
莫娜
明科夫→我想你
伊格刃匏官利→M入theloveiorn.com
我
Oh...
的
My...
天
God.
@特e的鏊
This particular establishment...
咪
Mommy?
]事旱 艾蜜莉
It's OK, Emily.
e害怕
Don't be scared, OK, honey?
跟著@好心的阿姨
Just go with this nice lady,
我一壕突斫幽 好
and I'll come see you in a couple hours, OK?
好了 丫^ 勇敢c 好
All right. Be my brave girl, honey, OK?
阿文
Alvin!
阿文 他把我女ё吡
Alvin, they're taking my daughter!
阿文 他ё吡税蜜莉
Alvin, they took Emily.
我的X海一片混y
there is trouble in my mind
法外情真 第二季 第五集
有黑暗
There is dark
有黑暗，也有光明
There's dark,and there is light
主演：西蒙 克
o法o天
There is no order
一片混沌，充M罪
But there is chaos and there is crime
今夜o人w家
There is no one home tonight
在我X海里的帝
In the empire of my mind
。捍笮l 霍m德
Σ黄 _你清袅
Sorry to get you out of bed.
]P系
It's Ok.
我本想安|尼・翰R姆硖理@事旱
I wanted Anthony Hanram to handle this,
但是我系不上他
but I couldn't track him down.
你能想象一qo律整天只骱C
You'd think a defense attorney would carry a pager--
]P系 阿文 ]事
That's OK, Alvin, it's all right.
呃
Uh,
抱歉]法保你
sorry about the bail.
咱F在手^]那么多FX
We--we just don't have that kind of money in the house.
明天一早我就能把XR
So, uh, I'll get it for you first thing tomorrow morning.
露露
Lulu...
露露 能看著我
Lulu, could you look at me?
明天 你到援助中心
Tomorrow, at the clinic,
分配一下比^急的案子
distribute the cases that are pressing and
其他人照常工作
get continuances for the others.
好 在你回碇前我兔Φ
Right. I'll cover for you until you get back.
需要你忙
I need something else.
然
Sure.
麻┠闳ヒ惶Tk公室
I need you to go to the clerk's office
查一下有]有一女人
and find out if bail has been set
叫尼取た死鹊谋ａ
for a woman named Janine Crane.
她是l
Who is she?
她是和我一起
She's a woman who, uh...
被逮捕的那女人
the woman I was with when I got arrested.
嘿 杰克
Hey, Jake.
嘿
Hey.
你fR斯特森的事毫
So did you hear about Masterson?
我f地^z察官接了一O蔚陌缸
Yeah. I hear the D.A's got an open-and-shut case.
他抓了左撇子的女人
They caught the woman left handed.
得了吧
Come on.
你看 他雇了翰R姆退qo
Well, look, he hired Hanram to defend himself.
@回 他又有好褪
Once again, he's in good hands.
@回真的是相乐
It's a pretty--pretty serious matter.
明[著 @女人f自己是清白的
Apparently, the woman claims she's innocent.
但我相肯定她一定有事
I'm pretty certain she had a hand in it.
杰克 我昨天_了合伙人h
So, Jake, we had a partner's meeting yesterday
了一下你的事
to discuss your deal.
好
Great.
所以你F在是授薪合伙人了（^e于收益分t合伙人）
So you are an income partner.
m然]有投票
You--you don't have a vote yet,
但你的薪水
but your salary is as we agreed,
是我之前f好的金
and your bonus will be
你表F而定
commensurate to your performance.
好的 要先理的案子是哪
OK. So what's the first order of business?
赫斯勒・科林尼斯
Hessler Kleaners.
在他X得出售特SI嘀前
Before they commit to franchising,
我需要做一法律用娴目尚行苑治
we need a legal feasibility study,
法人M文件
incorporation documents,
有一份授予特SI嗟fh范本
and a master franchise agreement
周四上午之前要完成
by Thursday morning.
]}
Done.
祝R你 杰克
Congratulations, Jake.
祝R你
Congratulations.
Π文的事焊械胶苓z憾
Yeah, and it's, uh, it's a shame about Alvin.
嗯
Yeah.
希望@件事能M快了Y
Sure hope he gets off.
哈洛f先生
Mr. Hallowell?
叫我塞思
Oh--Seth.
塞思 好的
Seth. OK.
@件事τ谠助中心碚f事P重大
Well, this is a very serious problem for the clinic.
我董事成T
All of us on the board,
都很P注
we're all very, very concerned.
我M我所能兔μ理的
Well, just let me know what I can do to help.
目前 r工作接手援助中心
For now, take over the clinic.
代表援助中心
Be the face of the place.
r不要提阿文
Now, make no mention of Alvin.
我M可能把公P注的焦c
We're going to do our best
陌文身上移_
to spin this away from Alvin
D而投射向你
and onto you.
什么
Excuse me?
你的形象正是我F在需要的
Your image is what we need right now.
像你@ 已婚又有烈家庭^念的人
Someone like you, married with family values,
付媒w
to meet with the press,
我的意思是 椭我渡^yP
I mean, to help us through this time.
阿文只是被起V
Alvin has just been charged,
]有被定罪
he's not convicted of anything.
他的合同里明了`反功德行l款
Moral turpitude clause, it's in his contract.
你的合同里也有
It's in yours, as well.
@里是主要理家庭法律事盏脑助中心 路易斯
I mean, this is a family clinic, Louise--
e 我明白 我理解 我只是f
Oh, no, I know, I understand that, I'm just saying--
我雇你是作檫@中心的副主任
You were hired as associate director of this clinic.
F在是你履行的r候了
It's time for you to do that job.
露露 嘿
-Lulu. -Hey.
阿文的事
So, this whole Alvin thing's
有c^了哈
a little crazy, huh?
如果你我的 我J楹苡薮
I think it's stupid, if you ask me.
真的 槭裁
Really? Why?
然了 竟然去按摩院
Yeah, going to a massage parlor?
你θグ茨υ旱哪腥擞幸庖
You have a problem with a man going to a massage parlor?
我α璩咳c起床去保阿文有意
I have a problem with getting up at 3 a.m. to bail Alvin out,
我σ樗不能控制自己
and I have a problem taking on all of his cases
而要我接受他的工作有意
because he can't control himself.
好吧
Yeah.
我@去我k公室了
Well, I'll--I'll be in my office.
尼克 十c半有庇oC要你去
Uh, Nick, you have a shelter hearing at 10:30.
布恩特・威科克斯
Bryant Wilcox.
好
OK.
芭芭拉
Barbara!
很抱歉打_你
I'm sorry to bother you.
e ]的事
No, no, it's no problem, I--
我只是最近手^
I just, uh, I've got a lot of work
事河悬c多 所以
going on right now, so--
那改天吧
Maybe later.
什么事
Well, what is it?
我能
Can I just--
你臀忙
please, uh, I need some help,
@事何]法跟援助中心的人_口
and I can't talk to anybody at L.S.P. about it.
到我k公室吧
OK, why don't you come on in my office?
你X_著
Is your computer on?
_著 怎么了
Yeah, why?
能上W
Uh, can you go on the internet?
接到“相思”@W站
Punch in "thelovelorn."
怎么了
Why?
c_看看
Just punch it in.
是_玩笑是怎么的
Is this some kind of joke?
B上了 嗯
-Got it? -Yeah.
好 滑到W最下面
OK, scroll down to the bottom.
你@照片拍的不e
That's a good picture of you.
c
Click it.
看看@胖蠢，她要跟我做勰
芭芭拉 我很抱歉
Barbara, l'm sorry.
天 太^分了
Gosh, that sucks.
我常上城紊砭W
Yeah, I used to go to this site, iron city singles,
（匹堡在十九世o初因冶行Il_而被Q殇F城）
我]有X 所以在k公室待到很晚
I'd stay late at work 'cause I don't have a computer.
之就是我遇到一男的
Anyway, I met this guy there.
W名是lgnatiusjreilly
lgnatiusjreilly,
出自《笨伯盟》@本 挺不e的
you know,from "Confederacy Of Dunces," which is a great book,
@是另一回事毫
but another story.
我的W名是莫娜明科夫 我_始在W上聊天
I was myrnaminkoff, and we started chatting,
我不知道
and, I don't know,
那N有人可以
there was something about it,
就只是聊天
having someone to talk to, just talk,
不到面 也不用互相u^足
without being judged or stared at.
我只是X得
I just felt like,
@么Lrg以
for the first time in a very, very long time,
第一次有人真正我AV
someone was really listening to me,
P心我
considering me.
你是坐下
Why don't you, uh--
@N情r持m了多Lrg
how--how long did this go on for?
月
A few months.
我_始聊天
We started chatting.
聊^状沃后他要我的照片
He asked for my picture after a couple of chats,
然后我f我不o的
and I said that I wouldn't give it to him
因槲抑前v^
because l've had experiences with men
似的情r
when they see me.
我也不想他看到我真的幼
And I didn't want him to imagine me like I am, I guess.
然后有一天 我o他l了]件
And then at one point I emailed him.
跟他f了我的w型
I told him about my size.
他f]P系
He said that it was fine,
他自己也不完美
that, uh, he wasn't perfect, either.
后砦奈那里找砹苏掌
So I had my mom take that picture,
在k公室呙韬蟀lo了他
and I scanned it at work, and then I sent it.
昨晚他l]件o我我
And then last night he emailed me to go
去相思W站看一下
to the lovelorn site.
我很z憾 芭芭拉
I'm so sorry, Barbara.
我想把照片撤下 杰克
I want it down, Jake.
我不怪你
Yeah, well I don't blame you,
但是 @很yk
but, uh, listen, this is a tough case.
我可以主ur
I mean, we can argue defamation,
但是他也有他的嗬
but he's got his rights.
我只想把照片撤下
I want it down.
e管我 放_我
Leave me alone!Leave me alone!
^ 布恩特 ^戆
Come on, Bryant, come on out.
噢
Damn!
斯洛特小姐 @孩子的律在哪
Miss Solt, where is this child's counsel?
我砹 法官大人
I'm here, your honor.
他F在已不受控制了 法林先生
He is out of control, Mr. Fallin.
R上他安o 不然我就庭P
Calm him down or you're sanctioned!
^ ^
Hey, come here, come here.
哦
Ow! Ow!
放_我
Let go of me!
放_我 放我下 你o我^
-Let go of me! Put me down! -Come here, you.
好了 著
All right, listen.
R上o我站好 不S吵[
You're going to stand here and you're going to be quiet, OK?
到底怎么回事
What is going on?
他F在怎么了
What is he doing now?
他正在抽搐
He's having a convulsion.
詹姆斯 抱歉
James, excuse me, we have 3 families
又有上三新案子M
coming in with new cases.
你能接一下
Will you take them?
我已忙得不可_交了
I'm swamped.
大家都一
We all are.
@些
Those...
大家好
Hey, everybody.
露露 跟思^之后 我要跟你一下
Lulu, after I meet with Seth, I need to see you.
社服部 抱歉您久等了
Social Services, sorry to keep you waiting.
天 阿文 我都很心你
Gosh, Alvin, um, we've been concerned.
援助中心扛^去的
The clinic is going to get through this.
P于你
Well, about you.
思 @事了Y的
Seth, this will all clear up.
我F在面R的只是三等p罪的指控
I'm facing a third degree misdemeanor
而且案子并不一定站得住_
and they have a weak case.
著 阿文
Listen, Alvin,
是你一手k了@地方
you built this place.
你成就了@里 @是哪愕慕嵌瘸霭l
You made it what it is. It's your vision.
你要我退出
You want me out of here?
阿文 不是我
Alvin, it's not me.
你的合同里包含道德l款
Your contract contains a morals clause.
董事Q定在事情了Y前你r停
The board wants to suspend you until this is resolved.
我是董事成T 是我M了董事
I'm on the board. Hell, I created the board.
要是我]被定罪
If I'm not convicted of a crime,
董事f我的不是
how can the board argue that I did anything wrong?
你在一家按摩院被警察抓了
You were arrested in a massage parlor.
阿文 你的_做e事了
Alvin, you did something wrong.
不 思 我]e
No, Seth, I didn't.
露露 嗯？
Lulu. -Yeah.
我需要你代理吉妮・克m
I need you to represent Janine Crane.
槭裁
Why?
社服部ё吡怂的女喊蜜莉
Social services took her daughter Emily.
他把她安置在庇o所
They put her in a shelter and they're
他fr不能她x_
making noises about not letting her out.
你知道 阿文 哈洛f先生f
Ugh. Alvin, you know, Mr. Hallowell said that--
@不是思的法援中心 是我的
This isn't Seth's clinic, it's mine.
著 她已是我的客袅
Listen, she's already a client.
五年前 我代理了吉妮的庇oC
5 years ago, I represented Janine in a shelter hearing.
你不X得@是利益_突
You don't think this is a conflict?
我已跟她^@}了
I've already discussed this with her.
她已明放了可能存在的利益_突
She's waived whatever conflict there might be.
另外 我已被r停了
Besides, for now, I'm suspended.
@孩子急病突l
He had a seizure.
已有人他去匹堡市立t院了
They took him to Pittsburgh County.
他母H呢
Where's the mother?
在服刑 她四周前因槎酒贩缸锶氇z
In prison--she was arrested for drugs 4 weeks ago.
]有父H的下落
The father's not in the picture.
在他母H被捕之前他住在哪
Where's he been staying since the mother's arrest?
^去月他一直跟他的阿姨x
He's been staying with his aunt Cheryl for the
住在一起
past couple of months.
她接他一起住是因
She took him in because the mother
他母H一旦嗨起砭字懿换丶
would be gone for weeks at a time getting high,
但@阿姨基本管不了他
but the aunt can't handle him.
@就是我今天_庭的原因
That's why we were in court today.
孩子的母H有做tQ定的行槟芰
Can the mother make medical decisions for the child?
她在吸毒的恢推
She's finding recovery challenging.
就在上周 身w被z出毒品
Just last week, they found drugs in her cell.
法林先生 我F在指定你獒t行楸Oo人
Mr. Fallin, I need to appoint a medical guardian.
你X得你能承@任
You think you can handle the responsibility?
我
Well, I...
威科克斯女士f
Ms. Wilcox said her sister Cheryl
她的妹妹可以做tQ定
could make medical decisions.
那法林先生你就作榕Rr的tOo人
Oh, Mr. Fallin will step in as temporary medical guardian.
我T再通知你新的Crg
I'll have my clerk notify you of the new hearing date.
b于@孩子的情r 庭上述M量蚊髁
Be prepared to fully brief the court on the child's condition.
事情很 吉妮
It's pretty simple, Janine.
你A了官司 就能^mB育你女
You win your case, you'll probably keep your daughter.
否t 她就要^m待在收BC
Otherwise, she will end up in foster care.
我J槟闶窍腽B育艾蜜莉的
I'm assuming that you want to keep Emily.
然
Of course.
好的
All right.
他z查你的居住l件
Well, they're going to look into your housing situation,
有什么是我需要知道的
so is there anything that l need to know?
P于
About?
你住的地方
Where you live.
我的公寓
Um, in an apartment.
就在按摩院上面
Above my business.
你是f你就住在那什么巧
Oh, you mean you live right above the--
Yeah.
怎么了
What?
你槭裁醋鲞@一行
Why do you do this?
槭裁
-Why? -Yeah.
榱隋X 能槭裁
Money. Why else?
我不知道
I don't know.
我不是榱隋X工作 所以
I mean, I don't work just for money, so...
那很好
Well, good for you.
你什么意思
What does that mean?
]上大W
No college.
也]上高中 真的 ]父母 ]X
No high school, really. No parents, no money.
我并不是想o你v一悲K的故事
You know, I'm not trying to tell you a sob story,
但是看看你
but looking at you, I--I'm guessing
我猜一定有人很勰
somebody out there loves you,
湍
helps you.
但是 我是f 出u肉w
But, still, I mean, selling, uh--
你的很多客人都是已婚人士
a lot of the men that you see are--are married.
那不是我的e
That's not my fault.
那他的妻子呢
What about their wives?
我也不能f@是她的e @
I can't say it's their fault, either.It's...
有些男人就是@
the way some men are.
就只是性而已 W森夫人
It's just sex, Mrs. Olsen.
]什么意思
It's not fun.
我也不喜g 但@是我\生的手段
I don't like it, but it's something I know how to do.
Mommy!
艾蜜莉 我好想你 我想你
Emily, oh I missed you. I missed you.
F在不能她走
They can't release her.
槭裁
Why not?
吉妮]有被定罪
I mean, Janine hasn't been convicted of anything yet.
_庭之后是什么情r我不清楚
We don't know what's going to happen with the court case,
艾蜜莉眼下是要待在庇o所
so for now, Emily has to stay in the shelter.
我找沃瑟曼t生
Dr. Wasserman l'm looking for.
沃瑟曼t生 我是尼克・法林
Dr. Wasserman, I'm Nick Fallin.
布恩特・威科克斯  你是他的tOo人
Bryant Wilcox, right? You're his medical guardian?
That's right.
他的片子@示]有用}瘤
His films show no aneurisms,
也]有X瘤 他不是dBl作
no brain tumors, he's not an epileptic,
并]有什么明@病
nothing normally associated
造成他之前的抽搐
with the type of seizure that he suffered,
但他的血液化研究Y果@示
but the results from his blood work
血U量是85
show a lead level of 85.
很高
Is that high?
高于10就已很危U了
Anything above 10 is considered dangerous.
那他@拥脑因是
Well, uh, how could it get like that?
P于含U涂料的法案
The projects are full of lead paint
早在啄昵熬妥U了
that should have been abated years ago.
孩子`食ζ
The kids eat the paint chips,
或是吸入γ娴幕m和碎屑
inhale dust that flakes from the wall.
父母意R到的r候 孩子病已很重了
By the time the parents realize it, their child's already sick.
@能造成他的抽搐
Could it have caused his seizure?
他的抽搐 是一N烈的C能亢M
His seizure, his intense hyperactivity,
他的言Z功能和生Ll育t
his speech and developmental delay,
有神系yp
and neurological damage.
能治
Can it be treated?
螯合治能M可能的p少
Chelation therapy attempts to drain the
血液中的U含量
lead particles from the blood.
但是病人很痛苦 而且效有限
It's painful, and only so effective.
嗨
Hi.
得我 在法庭上 我叫尼克
Remember me from court? My name's Nick.
布R恩特喜g肀
Bryant likes to hug.
我需要他t的副本
I need a copy of his records.
我要把他的接受治的搜集完整
I'm trying to put together a medical history.
我也一
So are we, but we don't even know
但我F在不知道他有]有自己的小嚎漆t生
if he has a pediatrician,
也系不到他母H
and we can't locate the mother.
我想你兔βj到他母H
We were hoping you'd know where she is.
好的
Sure.
私聊室
莫娜
明科夫→伊格刃匏官利，在幔
伊格刃匏官利→嗯？
莫娜明科夫→我要你撤N我的照片和]件
莫娜
明科夫→我付你三百美元
伊格刃匏官利→一千
莫娜明科夫→五百
伊格
刃匏官利→九百
莫娜明科夫→六百
伊格刃匏官利→要F金，
九c
在W克m的快姆餐^外，我去找你
你能告V我你鹤拥男嚎漆t生的名字
Can you tell me the name of your son's pediatrician?
一\所
Some clinic.
就在福布斯和W克m大街那
The one up on Forbes and Oakland.
我Р既R恩特去那嚎床
Took Bryant there.
我能跟你妹妹x系
Well, should I just ask your sister Cheryl?
布R恩特的事
About Bryant?
她]他看^t生
She never took him to no doctor.
你母子不住一起的r候也是你他去的
You took him even when he wasn't living with you?
他是我的孩子
He's my kid.
那你得o布R恩特看病
Do you remember the name of any of the doctors
的t生的名字
that treated Bryant?
你需要的 就去我的律
You need anything like that, you talk to my lawyer.
你的公Oqo人怎么有
Why would your public defender
你鹤拥尼t呢
have a medical record on your son?
不是他 是我的私人律
Not him, my private guy.
h森先生 R克・h森
-Mr. Hansen. -Marc Hansen?
好吧 xx
Oh, OK. Thank you.
我和h森先生 我正淦鹪V房|
And me and Mr. Hansen-- we're suing the landlord
因楹U超说耐苛
on account of the lead paint.
我出去的 就能把布R恩特Щ Π
When I get out, I get Bryant back, right?
@要由法庭Q定
That's for the court to decide.
布恩特・威科克斯 然
Bryant Wilcox? Sure.
U中毒 卡特街的目
Lead case. Carter Street projects.
有好多生病的孩子 你怎么知道他
A lot of sick kids. How do you know him?
我是他的代理人
I'm representing him.
她在Oz 我要安置他
His mom's in jail, and I'm placing him.
Oz
Jail?
到@消息真是好 Π
Nice to let her lawyer know, huh?
但@就是接人身害案子
But that's the kind of clients
常要付的客
you deal with when you do personal injury.
生意怎么 挺好
-How's business, man? -It's fine.
你真是到跑啊
You've been all over the place.
我芍芮按螂到你的新律所
I tried calling you two weeks ago at the new firm,
但是被D接到你老爸那
but the phones forwarded me back to your Dad's place.
我又在一起工作了
Well, we're working together again.
F在律所叫法林&法林
It's called Fallin and Fallin.
在我替布R恩特找到安置家庭之前
So before I can find Bryant a home,
我需要他的t
I need a copy of his medical records.
@孩子需要被安置到
Is there a chance this kid might
集w家庭之的地方
need to be placed in some kind of group home?
能蛱峁┨厥夥盏募彝 ]e
Special needs home, yeah.
@δ愕陌缸佑椭 索r能得更多X
That helps your case. Worth more money.
塔拉 臀野巡既R恩特・威科克斯的Y料陀∫环
Tara, could you please make a copy of the Bryant Wilcox file?
朱莉怎么 美依f
-How's Julie? -Beautiful as ever.
我向他好
Say hello to her for me.
周六晚上
Hey, why don't you come over for dinner
到我家吃吧
Saturday night, huh, you know?
好久]了 她也挺想你的
It's been too long. I know she'd love to see you.
好 ]} 我很芬膺^去
Yeah, it'd be great. I'd like to do that.
我今晚就塔拉把布R恩特的t
All right, I'll have Tara messenger
鹘o你
a copy of Bryant's meds to you tonight.
好
All right.
能l到法律援助中心
Can you--can you send them to legal services?
你要在那焊啥嗑
How much longer you got to do that?
我只是^砜纯醇妮
I just came by to see how things
和艾蜜莉的事涸趺恿
are going with Janine and Emily.
艾蜜莉F在r由社服部的人照看
Uh, well, Social Services is keeping Emily for now.
不能把她弄出
You can't get her out?
诶铩に孤逄夭煌意
No. Laurie Solt said no, so...
阿文
Alvin...
你真要榱诉@G掉工作
are you really going to lose your job over this?
地^z察官o我提了V交易
The D.A' s offering me a deal.
只要我把吉妮供出
I give up Janine, and they reduce
他就起V我p罪
my charge to a violation.
那很好
Great.
就@么做吧
Well, do it.
他我撒e
Well, they're asking me to lie.
吉妮和我之g 砭筒皇墙疱X交易
Janine and I--it was never about money.
我]付^Xo她
I never paid her.
阿文 你知道 你@么努力工作
Alvin, you know, you work so hard and--
大家都很敬重你
and everyone respects you,
我不明白 槭裁
I don't understand. I mean, why?
你槭裁慈
Why would you go--
@跟e人有什么P系
What's one got to do with the other?
就因槲业男陨活 我就不是一合格的律了
Am I any less of a lawyer because I have a sex life?
然不是 但我f的是妓女
No, but--but the prostitute is what I'm talking about.
她是妓女 但跟我在一起r不是
She may have been a prostitute, but she wasn't with me.
lgnatiusjreilly
lgnatiusjreilly?
你是l
Who the hell are you?
我是杰克・斯塔卡
I'm Jake Straka.
@是勒令停止通知函（ι嫦悠墼p的人士寄l的法律文件）
And this is a cease and desist letter.
什么
What?
Myrnaminkoff希望你P]自己的W
Myrnaminkoff wants off your web site.
我希望今晚午夜之前撤掉你l布的照片
I expect it to be down by midnight tonight.
你是在W上跟我s到@旱娜
You're the one that told me to come here?
]e
Yeah, that's right.
我的X呢
Where's my money?
你拿不到 傻蛋
You don't get it, dumb ass.
要是你不把照片撤掉
lf you don't take this down,
我就把你和你父母告到破a
I'm going to sue the crap out of you and your parents, OK?
是
-Oh, really? -Yeah.
我的X呢
Where's my money?
你能得到的只有一鲫P系 兄弟
All you're getting is a lawsuit, pal.
伙
Fellas!
@耍我
This guy posed as a fat chick.
兄弟 @只是法律m好
Look, guys, this is a legal dispute, OK?
我才不管是什么
I don't care what it is.
e激
Hey, take it easy.
他就是那f要o我600K的人
He's the one that promised us 600 bucks.
e激 好
Hey, take it easy, OK? Just take it--
我就要X
Hey, I want my money.
好
OK?
把@吃了
Eat this.
芭芭拉
Barbara.
我跟Ignatiusjreilly面了
I met with Ignatiusjreilly.
他不同意撤掉照片
So he's not gonna take the pictures down.
嗯
OK.
咱直接起V他
So we're gonna go after him in court.
真要@么做
We are?
我R上向法院提交λ的特e禁令
I'm gonna hit him with a petition
今天就舅到庭
for special injunction, haul him into court today.
基于什么理由 ur
-On what basis? -Defamation.
但是你f 不 那W上f
-Yeah, but you said -No, the site states
你想跟他上床
that you wanted to have sex with him.
并配著你的照片 @就是ur
That goes to your character. That is defamation.
首先 我要他P]W
So, first we're gonna get him to take the site down,
然后我正式起V他
then we're gonna sue him.
要是他]有可用于绦匈r的存款 就绦兴的其他a
If he doesn't have any money, we go after his assets.
要是他]有
If he doesn't have any assets,
就要求绦兴父母的a
we go after his parents' assets.
他父母
His parents?
我去了市里 我也JR人
Yeah, I went to Pitt, too, and I know people.
我要他被W校_除
So I'm getting him thrown out.
他是大W生
He's a college student?
很抱歉 他是
Yeah, I'm sorry, he is.
我要好好收拾他
I'm gonna bury his ass.
我以后到你的信息就R上s砹
I came as soon as I got your message.
病情更乐
Uh, this seizure was worse.
他F在是昏迷B
He's in a coma.
他醒^淼 Π
But he's gonna come out of it, right?
F在很yf
It's too early to know.
我拿到了他的t
I have a copy of his medical records.
上面@示上月他的血U量持m上升
They say that his lead levels kept increasing
之后有所下降
up until the last month and then leveled off.
下降代表
Well, if they leveled off,
他x_了U污染h境
that means the exposure probably ended.
需要Q定是否^m生命S持系y的r候
If a decision needs to be made about life support--
不 我
No. I--
什么
No, what?
不 我
Just no. I--
阿文 M戆
Alvin, come on in.
著
Listen--
阿文 你不需要
Alvin, you don't have--
吉妮和我有性P系
Janine and I have an adult relationship.
很@然
Clearly.
我的意思是
What I mean is,
啄昵 我x婚 r我是她的代理人
years ago, after I got divorced, I represented her.
我相了一段rg 互相喜g
We spent time. We liked each other.
你槭裁锤我f@些
Why are you telling me this?
我]付Xo她 诶
I never paid her, Laurie.
她不是那N
She was not--is not-- the kind of person
那N大家以榈
who deserves to be known just as another--
那N什么
Another what?
妓女
A prostitute.
那她算什么
Then what is she?
她是好女人
She's a kind woman.
一好
A good mother.
她理跟她的女涸谝黄
She deserves to have her child--with her.
要是她MOz了呢
And if she goes to prison?
那是另外一回事毫
Well, then that's another story.
在犯罪指控Q定之前
But until the criminal charges are resolved,
槭裁床蛔她娘z
why not allow her to have the time
待在一起呢
she should have with her daughter?
好
OK.
xx
Thank you.
埃文 嗯
-Alvin? -Yeah?
就算你o她X了又怎么
If you paid for it, so what?
辛西I・威科克斯
-Cynthia Wilcox? -Yeah?
我是尼克・法林 我之前通^
Hi, I'm Nick Fallin. We spoke earlier.
他怎么
How is he?
你的公寓做^w涂料含U量y
Um, have you ever had your apartment tested for lead paint?
l生部T有人磉^
The Department of Health came through.
他有什么lF
And what did they find?
她跟我f]事
Told me it was clean.
好 在布R恩特跟你在一起的r候
OK. In the time that Bryant was with you,
你有主要到他行樯系
did you ever notice
一些化
any kind of change in his behavior?
他退步了
He was just going backwards.
已W的|西也忘了
Forgetting stuff he already knew.
B衣服也不能自己穿了
Boy couldn't even dress himself anymore.
我手上有布R恩特的血蟾
I have the records of Bryant's blood tests
z查的rg一直持m到你姐姐被捕
the weeks leading up to your sister's arrest.
是你他去血的
Did you take him for those tests?
不 都是米里姆他去
No. Myriam did all that.
就算她在外面嗑嗨了
Even when she was out binging,
但是每次她都回
she'd always make sure she'd come by
Р既R恩特去\所
to take Bryant to the clinic.
她_有她的} 但她是好
She's got her problems, but she's a good mother.
好 xx
Great. Thank you.
艾米 o我陀∫环菥Wj侵犯[私嗟陌咐
Amy, I need a copy of the cases on internet privacy law, OK?
杰克 我看了一下你整理的
Jake, look, I took a look at these Kessler Kleaner papers
P斯勒・科林that you prepared. Um--
好
OK.
我]法拿o我爸
I can't give them to my father.
很差
They're bad?
不太好
Well, they're not great.
好 我按r搞定的
OK, I'll have them done on time.
你在忙什么
What are you working on?
芭芭拉・辛斯基碚椅
Uh, Barbara Ludzinski came by to see me.
她和W上的某人又c}
She--she got into this relationship with this guy on the net,
@人羞辱她
and he humiliated her, so I'm just trying
我在想k法@人把WP]
to get him to take the site down.
赫斯勒的案子你需要褪
Do you need a hand with that Hessler case?
不 不 我很快就好
No, no. I'm on top of it.
我可以接^ 不
-I could take it over. -No.
需要我兔μ理辛斯基的事
Do you want me to help with the Ludzinski problem?
不 @是我自己的事
No. This is my thing.
那好吧
All right.
艾米 我需要判例的陀〖
Amy! Damn it, I need a copy of the case law, OK?
xx
Thank you.
xx你兔ψ艾蜜莉回
For getting them to give Emily back to me.
你得知道@可能只是r的
You know that might only be temporary?
一旦你被定罪 我知道
-If you're convicted -I know...
我有麻┝
I'm in trouble.
地^z察官
The D.A.--
他向那新淼呐孩豪钍 要她作C
they're pressuring that new girl, Lee, to testify.
他也在向我施加毫
They're pressuring me, too.
我]要^你的X
But I never asked you for money.
]人相信的
Nobody wants to believe that.
他李f什么她都f的
Look, Lee's gonna say whatever they want her to say.
她才19 很害怕
She's 19. She's scared.
吉妮 她把我都供出淼
Janine, she could implicate both of us.
你要接受交易
You're gonna take a deal?
我明白我z的P系并不是
I know our relationship wasn't like
他希望我f的那
they want me to say it was,
但我知道你是做哪一行的
but I also know how you make your living,
有]有我的C言
and they're gonna get you for that--
他都o你定罪的
with or without my help.
亨利・利恩Ⅳ辛斯基小姐的
Henry Lean posted Miss Ludzinski's
私人通信和照片
personal correspondence and photograph
l布在W上 并附上@拥祟}
on a website under a heading which read,
“@死胖子想跟我上床”
"Check out this fat loser who wants to get it on with me."
@是在暗示辛斯基小姐
Now, this insinuates that Miss Ludzinski
自愿c陌生人l生性P系
is willing to have sex with a complete stranger,
依T法 已成ur
and is therefore, under common law, defamation, per se.
此怎v
How so?
自18世o起公_Q一女子是
Well, a claim that a woman is unchaste is defamatory
不的便成法律意x上的ur
as a matter of law, and has been since the 1700s.
法官大人
Judge...Ahem.
我不是律 但正在x法律A科
I'm not a lawyer, but I am pre-law.
我都知道法第一修正案的涵x
We have covered what the First Amendment means.
所以我知道 一旦辛斯基小姐
So, I know that as soon as Miss Ludzinski
自愿把照片o我
gave me that material,
我就有喟凑瘴易约旱囊庠讣右允褂
I was allowed to do whatever I wanted with it.
我^我的法律老
Now, I asked my law professor,
他跟我f
and he told me that, uh, she--
辛斯基小姐]有
"Miss Ludzinski has no reasonable
保o其[私的期待可能性
"expectation of privacy.
目前的判例已明_C了@一c
"It's been well established by the courts already."
@是他f的原
I mean, that's what he told me.
杰克
Jake?
杰克 你已M力了
Jake, you did your best.
M力了
My best?
我竟然被一M大W的毛^小子收拾了
Just got my ass handed me on a platter by a college student?
你跟那小（混蛋）
-Well, uh -did you ever ask that little--
你跟那小
Did you ever ask that little--
你是否跟他f^不要把照片
Did you ever ask him to not show the letters
和通信oe人看
or the photos to anyone?
我不得了
I don't remember.
好好想想 的 到底跟他f^]有
Think, damn it. Did you ever ask him?
可能吧
I may have.
有我看^的通信
Is there any correspondence that I haven't seen?
我不得了
I don't remember.
我要申他的X作樽C
I'm gonna subpoena his computer.
@ 杰克 F在回k公室
-Listen, Jake -Look, just go back to work.
z查一下所有保存的|西
Check everything that you ever saved.
看一下有]有你要求他不要把照片拿oe人看的
See if you ever asked him not to show the letters to anyone.
我X得可能找不到
Well, I don't think I did.
去找 我就能以`反s定起V
Do it! We can claim breach of contract.
但是 杰克 就@么做 好吧
-But, Jake -Look, just do it, OK?
我再找你
I'll come by later.
我知道你一直在喂布R恩特吃ζ
I know you've been feeding Bryant paint chips.
我不明白你在f什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
@就能解槭裁床既R恩特的血U量
Then explain to me why Bryant's lead levels
在你被O禁前的那段rg仍然持m上升
kept increasing the month before your incarceration.
我不知道
Well, I don't know.
那死公寓到都是U
There was lead all over that damn apartment.
最后一月他并]有在你的公寓住
He wasn't living in your apartment that last month.
他跟你妹妹住在一起
He was living with your sister,
而她的公寓的U污染zy是正常的
and her apartment is lead-free.
我不知道你在f什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
你一周接布R恩特一次
You would pick Bryant up once a week,
把他У侥的公寓 然后喂他ζ
and take him to your apartment and feed him paint chips.
仔r之后 你再_他去\所
A few hours later, you would take a drive to the clinic,
血
and he would get a blood test.
你了
You're crazy!
我要去告V地^z察官
I'm gonna go and talk to the D.A.
他]f@引ldB
He didn't say nothing about no seizures.
l 那律
-Who? -The lawyer.
h森
Hansen?
我Р既R恩特去做W前wz的r候
When I took Bryant to the doctor for his start of school check-up,
他f他U中毒
they said he had the lead.
跟我住一公寓的朋友f
So one of my friends in the building
我去找h森
said l should go see Mr. Hansen,
f他能臀乙些r
that he could get us some money.
但是h森先生sf
But Mr. Hansen said that--
我鹤拥难U量不蚋
that my boy's level was too low to be worth his time.
要是我能做c什么
But I could do stuff that could
就能拿到近百f的r
make the case worth a million dollars.
他跟你@么f的
He told you that?
Yeah.
他跟所有的母H都是@么f的
He told all the mothers that.
嘿
Hey.
你在@干嘛
What are you doing here?
就 忙案子
Just--just working on a case.
你呢
You?
偷e
Snuck in.
在大家都下班之后
After everybody was gone.
不想一人坐在家里
Didn't feel like sitting around my apartment.
我@周想了你的事
I thought about you this week.
在Oz的那晚
That night in jail.
我之前也待^Oz
I've been there before, you know.
因榭棺h被捕
Getting arrested for protests.
但是
But, uh,
如果是因橐恍┧饺说}M去 那感X
when you're in for something personal, it's--
很害怕
-Scary. -Yeah.
你在等待庭的r候
When you were awaiting trial,
他o你提了V交易
they offered you a deal, right?
但是]有接受
-But you didn't take it? -No.
槭裁
Why not?
我什么都]做e
I didn't do anything wrong.
嘿 哦 xx
-Hey. -Hi. Oh, thank you.
怎么
So?
我找不到
I can't find anything.
W上的你全都查^了
You looked everywhere on the site?
我]跟他f^不能e人看
Well, I--I never told him he couldn't show anyone else.
你_定你都查^了
You sure you looked?
硬P呢
What about your hard drive? Did you--
杰克 拜托
Jake, please.
我不想再找了 好
Um, I--I don't wanna look at this stuff anymore, OK?
我的意思是
I mean--
那就撒e 不行
-Lie. -No.
你只要f ]耗有
No, just say that maybe you have it on--
杰克 不 你看 芭芭拉 我
-Jake, no. -Look, Barbara, I--
我知道你是好意
I know you mean well.
^去@滋
And these last couple of days,
我矶疾恢道你能ξ
I never imagined that you would feel so strongly...
芭芭拉
Barbara--
@么好
about me.
你放下了手的一切
That--that--that you could-- could drop everything
@么嵝臀
and be so, I don't know, passionate?
他 他打了我
They--they beat me up.
我去他的r候
When I went to see them, they, uh--the kid
那孩子和他朋友
and his friends-- they--
把我打了 按倒在大街上
They--they punched me and they threw me on the ground, OK?
我F在是一家律所的合伙人
I--I am a partner in a law firm now.
他竟然那么做
And they--they did that.
所以我F在要求你做的事
So what--what I am asking you to do is--
只是榱俗你自己心理平衡
Let you get even, right?
榱俗你心理平衡
Let you get even.
Σ黄
Sorry.
不 是我`解了
No, I--I just misunderstood.
就@么算了吧 杰克 好
Let it go, Jake, OK?
如果我可以做到 你也行 就@么算了吧
If I can, so should you. Just--just let it go.
老兄 坐
Hey, man. Have a seat.
拿到我lo你的文件了
Get those files I sent you?
嗯
Yeah.
周六晚上
Saturday night
朱莉有馁M城淼呐笥
Julie has a friend coming in from Philly. Huh.
L得很漂亮
A very pretty friend.
是你跟你的客粽f
Did you tell your clients
她喂自己的孩子吃ζさ
to feed their children paint chips?
你在f什么
What are you talking about?
米里姆・威科克斯
Myriam Wilcox.
她跟我f如果她鹤拥难U量不蚋
She told me you wouldn't take her case
你就不接她的案子
until her son's lead levels were higher.
她的情r不蚱鹪V 但我我]跟她f
Her case wasn't worth enough, but I didn't tell her--
她f你跟那公寓的所有母H都@么f了
She said you told that to all the mothers in the building.
好吧
Yeah, well...
得你是在跟lf 尼克 好
Let's remember who you're talking with here, Nick,All right?
一正在服刑的a君子
This is a crack addict in prison.
得了吧
Come on.
你y道]有lF很奇怪
You didn't find it strange that the kid's levels
她第二次碚夷愕r候那孩子的血U量足足高了四倍
were 4 times higher on the second visit to your office?
我有37件@拥陌缸 尼克
I have 37 lead cases, Nick.
我又不是t生
I'm not a doctor, OK?
不注意@些抵
I don't monitor them all.
但你_跟她f血U量高
But you did tell her the case would be worth more
就能拿到更多的r
with higher lead levels.
我槭裁凑@兄弟
Why are we even having this conversation, man?
@女人蠢到喂自己的
I mean, if this woman is stupid enough
孩子吃ζ
to feed her kid lead paint, huh?
她要是@么傻
If she's that dumb,
我跟她f^的任何事都被`解
anything I say to her could be misconstrued.
`解
Misconstrued?
或者f她只是遵循你的建h
Or was she just following instructions?
我什么都]做e
I didn't do anything wrong.
尼克 你要是走漏了小子 你的客
Nick, if you make any noise about this, your client,
我的客 一大子憾家不到了
my client, won't see a dime.
@是你希望的
Is that what you want?
我跟地^z察官f^了
I spoke to the D.A.
只要你指Ch森
Testify against Hansen
他就不告你虐待和
and you won't be prosecuted for child abuse.
我不知道
I--I--I don't know.
他的目瞬皇悄 是h森
They don't care about you, they care about Hansen.
所以你要我告l我那公寓里的母H
And so I gotta--I gotta snitch on all the moms in my project?
Yes.
o她自己孩子喂U的那些人
The ones giving their kids the lead?
Yes.
好吧
OK.
有一件事
There's one more thing.
@是啥
What's this?
@是你自愿放H嗟奈募
It's your consent to relinquish parental rights.
什么意思
What's that mean?
意思是姆律意x上v
It means that you will no longer
你再也不是布R恩特的母H了
have legal standing as Bryant's mother.
你要把我的奈疑磉ё
You wanna take my baby away from me?
你要ξ业暮⒆舆@么做
You gonna do that to my boy?
你知道]有母H在他身
You know what it's gonna be like for him,
他未淼某砷L是什么
growing up without a mother?
知道
Yeah.
e再ξ也痪 ^Σ灰
Do not disrespect me! Ever!
嘿
Hey.
你穿@件睡衣看起砗芷亮
You look very pretty in these pajamas.
要是掉就更漂亮了
But you look a lot better out of them, huh?
布R恩
Brian--Brian.
你到底怎么了 露露
What the hell's wrong with you, Lulu?
我@一周都挺好的
I mean, I've been nice all week,
一起出去吃了晚餐
and, we, uh, went out to dinner.
一周三次打
And I called you at the office
到你k公室跟你f我勰
at least 3 times a day to tell you I love you.
你要我怎么做
I mean, what else do I have to do?
e再跟妓女胡搞
Stop having sex with hookers.
你f什么啊
What are you talking about?
你心里清楚
You know what l'm talking about.
我Y婚的字芮
A few weeks before we got married,
你在酒店I春
you got arrested for solicitation
被便衣警察抓了F行
by an undercover cop in the bar of the grand hotel.
你提出不做申q求 P款六百
You pled no contest got a $600 fine
Bm四周周六下去在圣s翰W校制教育
and 4 Saturday afternoons at John School.
根本不是你所f的在哥布的~外n程 是圣s翰W校
Not extra classes in Columbus-John school.
露露 你是不是X得我很蠢
-Lulu -Do you think I'm stupid?
看在上帝的份荷 我^T
I was a clerk, for God's sakes.
法院系y都有我的朋友
I've got friends all over the court system.
尼克跟你f的
Nick told you?
不是 但我知道是他代理你
No, but I know he represented you.
露露 我f
Lulu, listen--
我只是不知道
You know, I just don't know how
你怎么能跟e的女人做那N事
you could do that with other women.
跟妓女
Hookers.
然后回到家面ξ
And then come home to me.
不是你
It's not you.
你他fα 然不是我
You're damn right it's not me!
是你
It's you!
我承J我做了蠢事
It was a stupid thing I did.
只是婚前毫Υ
Like last-second jitters.
好吧
Oh, OK.
那你只有@一次
So then you only did this once?
Yes.
eξ胰鲋e 我中邪了
-Don't lie to me. -I mean I'm sick.
@是一N病B 我需要椭
It's a sickness. I need help.
]嘴 你才不是病
Shut up! You're not sick!
但是 布R恩 槭裁
But, Brian, why-- I mean, what are you--
你在外到底想で簏c什么
what are you looking for out there?
你到底要什么
Really, what the hell are you looking for?
要我x_
Should I leave?
不需要
No.
我接受了Vfh
I accepted a deal.
很抱歉到@些
I'm sorry to hear that.
赡 十二月就能出z了
Two years--I'll be out in 12 months.
我安置好艾蜜莉的
I'll make sure Emily gets a good placement.
就算不是李
If it wasn't Lee, it would have been
也是我的其他T工
one of my other employees
或者是某他抓到的客人
or one of the customers that were busted.
我不作C指J你的
I wouldn't have testified against you.
槭裁
Why not?
因
Because...
因槲]付你X
Because you don't pay me money.
阿文 啄昵
Alvin, a few years ago
孩子的事耗土宋
you helped me out with my kid.
每次有法律上的麻 我就打o你
Every time I had a legal problem, I called you.
]e
Right.
阿文
Alvin,
@就是你付X的方式
That's how you paid me.
B・R廷斯基：多x你兔
J・斯特拉卡：不客猓芭芭拉，一喝ズ纫槐怎
杰克 文件我看^了
Jake, I took a look at that work.
很好
It's very good.
我整晚]睡s工
I--I stayed up all night working on it.
r很有B
I was kind of, like, in the zone.
那很值得
Well, it was worth it.
赫斯勒很M意的
Hessler's gonna like it a lot.
我知道
I know.
芭芭拉・辛斯基的事涸趺恿
What happened with Barbara Ludzinski--that thing?
那熊孩子
Uh, the kid. I...
我把他搞定了
I dealt with him.
很好
Good.
M
Come on in.
他撤回了起V
They dropped the charges.
他的目耸羌妮 所以@事哼^去了
All they wanted was Janine, so it's behind us.
我有活阂忙
Well, I got a lot of work to do.
阿文 我很高d 真的很高d
Alvin, we're pleased. We're very pleased.
@永^m保留你援助中心主任的位
And we have no qualms in you retaining your position
我就]有什么疑]了
as director of the clinic.
xx
Thank you.
但你是被董事除名了
However, your seat on the board has been reassigned.
]有定罪啊
There was no conviction.
我是X得不太合m
We're not comfortable.
是我一手M建了@援助中心
I founded this clinic.
但是你得向董事
Right, but you report to the board.
章明_要求主任必是
The bylaws require that a director of the clinic
董事成T
be on the board.
@次的情r 副董事必@么做
In this case, the associate director will have to do.
什么
What?
W森被指定替代你在董事的位
Mrs. Olsen has been appointed in your place.
所以 你是援助中心的主任
So, you'll still be director of this clinic,
但是露露有⑴c董事Qh投票的嗬
but Lulu will have the vote upstairs.
我很抱歉 阿文 但我得考]捐助者的想法
I'm sorry, Alvin, but we have donors to think about.
法林先生
Mr. Fallin.
嗨 我
Oh, I--hi. I just--
探病rg已^了
visiting hours are--
我知道 工作忙一r走不_
Yeah, I know. I got held up at work.
]P系 不用著急
That's fine. Take your time.
反正你是唯一砜此的人
You're the only one to come visit him, anyway.
法外情真N吧
感x
人人影
翻g：M
制作：Michael Song
感x收看 下集再